knowledgedish.com 2018-10-23

# Privacy Policy | KnowledgeDish

This privacy policy sets out how KnowledgeDish.com uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website.  
KnowledgeDish.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

KnowledgeDish.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from March 5, 2017.

## **What we collect**

We may ask to collect the following information:

  * e-mail address (for use to send you the daily KnowledgeDish.com newsletter, which you can unsubscribe from at any time)

## **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## **How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. To learn more, we suggest consulting the Help section of your browser or taking a look at [the About Cookies website](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) which offers guidance for all modern browsers

## **Third Party Vendors**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/).

## **How To Opt-Out of third party data targeting**

If you prefer not to receive interest-based content and ads enabled by Quantcast, you can opt-out by clicking on the “Opt Out” link at either Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) (<http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#/>) or Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) (<http://optout.aboutads.info/#/>) . Quantcast is a member of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) and participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) Self-Regulatory Program. Each of these programs provides an opt-out feature where consumers can choose not to receive targeted advertising from any NAI or DAA affiliate. These links will take you to the NAI opt out (<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>) and the DAA opt out (<http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>) . If you are located in the European Union, you may prefer to use the EDAA opt out (<http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>) . After you opt-out, Quantcast will place a cookie on your browser that identifies you as having opted out. Then you will not receive interest-based content or advertisements enabled by Quantcast and Quantcast will not log your pattern of website visits or other online media consumption. Because the opt-out is cookie-based, your browser must be set to accept third party cookies. If you use multiple devices or browsers, you’ll have to opt out on each. If you delete the cookie, you will need to opt-out again.

## **Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
